<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hugh Sato</title>
    <link>https://proxycase.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hugh Sato</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 12:51:17 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://proxycase.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Ethics</title>
      <link>https://proxycase.github.io/posts/design-ethics/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 12:51:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://proxycase.github.io/posts/design-ethics/</guid>
      <description>Land Acknowledgement While I research, study, and practice my design craft, I embody a physical space that resides on the traditional homelands of the Three Fires Confederacy: Ojibwe, Odawa, and Potawatomi nations. Many other tribes have called this area home, including the Miami, Ho-chunk, Menominee, Sac and Fox. The site (Chicago, IL) where I work and live was a site of trade, gathering, and healing for more than a dozen other Native tribes, while the state of Illinois is currently home to more than 75,000 tribal members.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Process Part 2</title>
      <link>https://proxycase.github.io/posts/design-process-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 13:30:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://proxycase.github.io/posts/design-process-part-2/</guid>
      <description>In the previous post, I wrote about the first two stages in the design process: Discover and Define. I’ll be diving deeper into the second half of the process, where we take ideas that were distilled through the process, and are made into real designs, and real code.
Now that we’ve turned the Insights into “How might we’s,” there are a list of direct, actionable items to build out in our design program of choice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Process Part 1</title>
      <link>https://proxycase.github.io/posts/on-design-process-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2019 22:59:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://proxycase.github.io/posts/on-design-process-part-1/</guid>
      <description>While there are a variety of approaches to the design process, the overall purpose of the system remains the same:
To distill information, and to use it to develop appropriate solutions to a user problems. Ideally, the design tackles problems specifically identified from user contexts. By studying users, we solve problems in a measureable, evidence-driven manner.
Why used a defined design process? Real problems arise when products and services are developed without proper design research.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On designing my personal logo</title>
      <link>https://proxycase.github.io/posts/logo-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2019 13:10:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://proxycase.github.io/posts/logo-design/</guid>
      <description>In order to consider what it is that makes a logo, I first thought about the purpose, or why a logo needs to exist. While I’ve made logo designs in the past, I had made them for the express purposes of putting it on a portfolio website. In those cases, the logo serves a purpose of helping my personal brand or identity more visible, more memorable, and hopefully give the viewers a sense of personality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting as an 8th Light Design Apprentice</title>
      <link>https://proxycase.github.io/posts/first-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 14:15:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://proxycase.github.io/posts/first-day/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m Hugh, and today marks my first day as a Design Apprentice at 8th Light. For the last several years, I worked as a makerspace coordinator at the Northbrook Public Library, and helped design and build the makerspace from the ground-up, creating access to tools like 3D printers and laser cutters to the public. I created policies that shaped our services and opened up access to those outside of our own library, knowing that Northbrook is a unique area with plenty of resources to share.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://proxycase.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 21:37:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://proxycase.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hugh is a Design Apprentice at 8th Light, working on mastering his visual, UI, and UX design chops. Tech-artist on the side, ex-library-person (not librarian), and maker of all things, design has been a common theme in his journey.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>