<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hugh Sato</title>
    <link>https://proxycase.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hugh Sato</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 11:21:44 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://proxycase.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Html</title>
      <link>https://proxycase.github.io/posts/semantic-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 11:21:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://proxycase.github.io/posts/semantic-html/</guid>
      <description>Why write semantic HTML? There is a lot of confusing code out there in the world today. It’s not limited to HTML or CSS, but perhaps because these “languages” are so prolific, somewhat easy to learn, and because everyone has their own “style,”
I know that at least for me there wasn’t a lot of incentive to think too hard about doing everything properly as long as it worked.
When I started, I used generic divs for everything, and sections to hold those divs, and relied on classes for pretty much any sort of styling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Html Elements Part II</title>
      <link>https://proxycase.github.io/posts/html-elements-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 13:43:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://proxycase.github.io/posts/html-elements-2/</guid>
      <description>Part two of two on &amp;quot;all&amp;quot; of the html elements (that are not obsolete).
Images &amp;amp; Multimedia          &amp;lt;img&amp;gt; Used to embed images. Replaces the ancient &amp;lt;image&amp;gt; element. &amp;lt;img&amp;gt; so 2008, you so two-thousand-and-LATE.             &amp;lt;map&amp;gt; Used to create an image map (which is an area that is clickable, and might have multiple clickable spots, like a map, or an image that has clickable areas).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Html Elements Part I</title>
      <link>https://proxycase.github.io/posts/html-elements-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 13:43:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://proxycase.github.io/posts/html-elements-1/</guid>
      <description>In the following articles, I attempt to re-configure and define all the html elements in my own words and also try to figure out where they belong in relationship to each other. Part one of two.
The Head          &amp;lt;html&amp;gt; Is the root level of an himl document. All other elements are children of this element.             &amp;lt;head&amp;gt; Container for machine-readable information like metadata.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wallet UX Day 3</title>
      <link>https://proxycase.github.io/posts/wallet-ux-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 14:30:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://proxycase.github.io/posts/wallet-ux-day-3/</guid>
      <description>Tasks  Finalize competitive analysis synthesis Review survey data Review themes into insights Meet with “stakeholders” Begin wireframes for testing  Lots of discoveries Last night’s interview was really insightful because I was able to talk to someone who directly helps set up mobile applications for customers at a major bank. Her insights were really great, and while I did also ask her about her banking habits, there are a number of discoveries that she can identify as being problems:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wallet UX - Day 2</title>
      <link>https://proxycase.github.io/posts/wallet-ux-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 14:15:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://proxycase.github.io/posts/wallet-ux-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Tasks  Competitive Analysis synthesis Send out surveys Interviews Synthesize Interviews to Themes Start building deck  After sending out the survey last night, I got about 10 responses to a variety of questions about banking and budgeting. 100% of the responses were self-identified as Millenial, which makes sense but also the right audience for the project. I think what is most telling about the difference between my interviews and the survey-takers is that the interviewees tended to have entirely online banks, and the survey-takers had credit unions, and had also chosen banks based on their physical proximity to them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wallet UX Project - Day 1</title>
      <link>https://proxycase.github.io/posts/wallet-ux-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 16:35:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://proxycase.github.io/posts/wallet-ux-day-1/</guid>
      <description>Both interviews this morning/afternoon went well, and represented quite different experiences of how banking plays a role in our lives. KD, who is part of the older Millenial demographic, sought the help of a financial advisor along with her husband, to figure out future savings and investment opportunities. LN, a younger Millenial, used only one bank, the USAA, made for families of veterans and enlisted individuals. Both experiences were primarily or only web-based, and relied on the mobile app to interface directly with the bank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evidence Based (UX) Design</title>
      <link>https://proxycase.github.io/posts/evidence-based-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 14:41:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://proxycase.github.io/posts/evidence-based-design/</guid>
      <description>Last week, I had a design presentation which laid out the steps I took to build a fictional doggy daycare, and designed a website to interface with that business. While the project was internal and an experiment to push my skills, branding wasn’t a central focus of the project and I was ultimately asked about my color choices. Typically, I’m used to being given colors from clients from preexisting guidelines, but in this case, I had pulled up a color-theme making website and choose something that I thought just felt right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Ethics</title>
      <link>https://proxycase.github.io/posts/design-ethics/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 12:51:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://proxycase.github.io/posts/design-ethics/</guid>
      <description>Land Acknowledgement While I research, study, and practice my design craft, I embody a physical space that resides on the traditional homelands of the Three Fires Confederacy: Ojibwe, Odawa, and Potawatomi nations. Many other tribes have called this area home, including the Miami, Ho-chunk, Menominee, Sac and Fox. The site (Chicago, IL) where I work and live was a site of trade, gathering, and healing for more than a dozen other Native tribes, while the state of Illinois is currently home to more than 75,000 tribal members.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Process Part 2</title>
      <link>https://proxycase.github.io/posts/design-process-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 13:30:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://proxycase.github.io/posts/design-process-part-2/</guid>
      <description>In the previous post, I wrote about the first two stages in the design process: Discover and Define. I’ll be diving deeper into the second half of the process, where we take ideas that were distilled through the process, and are made into real designs, and real code.
Now that we’ve turned the Insights into “How might we’s,” there are a list of direct, actionable items to build out in our design program of choice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Process Part 1</title>
      <link>https://proxycase.github.io/posts/on-design-process-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2019 22:59:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://proxycase.github.io/posts/on-design-process-part-1/</guid>
      <description>While there are a variety of approaches to the design process, the overall purpose of the system remains the same:
To distill information, and to use it to develop appropriate solutions to a user problems. Ideally, the design tackles problems specifically identified from user contexts. By studying users, we solve problems in a measureable, evidence-driven manner.
Why used a defined design process? Real problems arise when products and services are developed without proper design research.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On designing my personal logo</title>
      <link>https://proxycase.github.io/posts/logo-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2019 13:10:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://proxycase.github.io/posts/logo-design/</guid>
      <description>In order to consider what it is that makes a logo, I first thought about the purpose, or why a logo needs to exist. While I’ve made logo designs in the past, I had made them for the express purposes of putting it on a portfolio website. In those cases, the logo serves a purpose of helping my personal brand or identity more visible, more memorable, and hopefully give the viewers a sense of personality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting as an 8th Light Design Apprentice</title>
      <link>https://proxycase.github.io/posts/first-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 14:15:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://proxycase.github.io/posts/first-day/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m Hugh, and today marks my first day as a Design Apprentice at 8th Light. For the last several years, I worked as a makerspace coordinator at the Northbrook Public Library, and helped design and build the makerspace from the ground-up, creating access to tools like 3D printers and laser cutters to the public. I created policies that shaped our services and opened up access to those outside of our own library, knowing that Northbrook is a unique area with plenty of resources to share.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://proxycase.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 21:37:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://proxycase.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hugh is a Design Apprentice at 8th Light, working on mastering his visual, UI, and UX design chops. Tech-artist on the side, ex-library-person (not librarian), and maker of all things, design has been a common theme in his journey.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>